https://sab.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting the School of American Ballet’s web site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used on this site.
Information We Collect
On sab.org you can order performance and event tickets, make a gift to SAB, register for auditions, enroll in our programs and send questions or comments to various administrative departments. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected include: name, address, business affiliation and address, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card information.
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our web site such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Safari, Internet Explorer, Chrome), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider.
How We Use the Information
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries, and to inform you other programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.
We may use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you programs or services.
Agents and contractors of SAB who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for SAB.
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.
SAB will never disclose personally identifiable information to any outside organization or companies that want to market products or services to you.
Cookies
To enhance your experience with our site, some of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.
We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience and save your password in password-protected areas.
Updates to this Policy
From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.
SAB Scholarship Fund
Support our talented young dancers
